errorhelpers.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy

ErrorHelpers > Website > Privacy Policy

errorhelpers.com respects the privacy of all vistors and website users. errorhelpers.com is committed to protecting each users privacy rights in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

The Privacy Policy explained below is for the use of errorhelpers.com only. We treat and respect your personally identifiable information and the information collected in connection with your activities on errorhelpers.com.

**1\. The Collection of Your Personal Information**

errorhelpers.com will not collect or use any information about you or any other visitor to our Web Site or share this information with any 3rd parties. There are no records kept of your individual activities. Your visit is completly anonymous with one exception, in order for errorhelpers.com to continuely grow, we do keep records of web site visits and may at times ask for personal information, giving you the option to opt in or opt out. In pursuant, the optional information collected please refer to section 2 below.

**2\. Commitment & Agreement **

If you make a purchase from a web site we recommeded, you most likely will be asked to provide your name, email and payment information. We may use information collected in the following ways:

  1. A Process, confirm and authenticate purchases.

  2. B Contact you to reconfirm or verify certainty of information collected.

  3. C Register you as a customer.

  4. D Open and continue a support account for you.

  5. E Send email reminders about new, existing, enhanced products or services.

  6. F Send information on beneficial offers or to obtain your feedback and help enhance existing features. 

  7. G Enable us to personalize content, advertising and promotions based on preferences, needs, suggestions, or recommendations.

  8. H Provide prior notice of termination of a trial period or an opportunity to extend a trial period, or advance notice of expiration of your software license.

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use (for example protect our intellectual property rights), and your compliance with the applicable End User License Agreement(s) contained within the [BRAND] software. We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the applicable law may require us to do so.

The information you provide will not be used for any other commercial purposes. INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE WILL NOT be sold, rented, leased or otherwise forwarded to any third party with the exception of our sales processor [CART], who will process your orders and distribute the goods or services that you have requested.

**3\. Use of Cookies**

errorhelpers.com use's **"cookies"** for the sole purpose of tracking affiliate referrals and conversion. errorhelpers.com does not save any personnal identifiable information from the use of cookies. Cookies are logs of data collected by websites and your browser to keep on your computer to facilitate your next visit to the site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many web sites use them. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. All parts of our website will function correctly if you disable cookies.

**4\. Links to Other Sites**

The errorhelpers.com may contain links to other web sites. errorhelpers.com does not monitor or control the content of such web sites or whether such web sites collect or process your personal information. Accordingly, errorhelpers.com assumes no responsibility or liability whatsoever for any kind of material available at such sites and recommends that you review the separate privacy policies of such sites.

**5\. Policy Changes**

errorhelpers.com may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. Any changes will be posted to this site, so we encourage you to continuously review our Privacy Policy.

**6\. Contact Information**

For questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us.

* * *
